http://www.hillwatch.com/privacy-policy.html

YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
By using our web site, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use the site.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means personally-identifiable information including, without limitation, your name, street address, telephone number, screen name and e-mail address.
Throughout this site, you may be asked for Personal Information so that you can register for a service, send electronic gift certificates, request information or mailings, buy a product or service from us, fill out a survey or for a variety of other reasons. Please be assured that Givex will not collect any Personal Information from this site unless and until you provide this information to us voluntarily.
This site may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (for instance, when you send an electronic gift certificate to a person, we will need you to provide recipient's name and e-mail or mailing address). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (eg., to send the electronic gift certificate) and we will not contact the third party again by e-mail unless and until the third party contacts us.
If you don't want us to have access to your Personal Information, please do not provide it while using our site. When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, including to your right to limit our use of the Personal Information (see "Who to Contact" below).
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
When you supply Personal Information on this web site, Givex will use it for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g. to enter you in a contest or to send you information).
OTHER INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT
Givex may collect other information about you during your visit to our site, but this information will not be linked to your Personal Information (that is, it is collected only in the aggregate in connection with all the users of our site, and will not be linked to you personally.) Such information may include:
information about your computer, such as your IP address (a number assigned to your computer whenever you use the Internet), the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site;
information about the areas you visit on our web site;
information about the products or services you buy through our web site.
COOKIES
Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer's hard drive when you visit a web site. Givex may use cookies to show how and when a user visits areas within our site so that we can see which areas are popular and which may need improvement. We also use cookies to help speed up your future activities at our site because the computer will remember that you have already provided Personal Information to us. Givex does not share Personal Information obtained through cookies with any third parties.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent.
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION
WE DO NOT SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES
Givex does not share any Personal Information with any third parties, except as provided in this Policy.
At times we may retain third parties to act as our agent to analyze data we collect on our web sites, including Personal Information, solely to help us improve our products and our web sites (e.g. if you request a sample, a market research company hired by us, may contact you concerning your experience with the product). In addition, if you order a product or service from us, we may share Personal Information with suppliers and other third parties to allow delivery of such product or service. These suppliers and other third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any other way.
Finally, please note that we will release Personal Information if in our opinion we are required or authorized to do so by or pursuant to law, or by a search warrant, subpoena, court order or other legal process.
MAILINGS AND OTHER CONTACT
Givex will not use your Personal Information to send you any mailings or to otherwise contact you unless you have expressly authorized us to do so. In addition, at any time you may let us know that you wish to discontinue such mailings or contact (see "Who to Contact" below).
CHILDREN
Givex is committed to protecting the on-line privacy of children, including young teens, and making the Internet safe for our users. To that end, no information should be submitted to or posted on this site by children under the age of 18 without their parent or guardian's permission. In addition, if a user younger than 18 wishes to send us Personal Information, he or she must first give us his or her parent's or guardian's e-mail address so that we can obtain their permission. No Personal Information will knowingly be accepted from a child under 18 before this permission is obtained.
If your child has already provided us with Personal Information, you may ask to see this information for the purpose of correcting it, or ask us to delete this information from our records entirely (see "Who to Contact" below.)"
SECURITY INFORMATION
We use state-of-the-art technology to keep your Personal Information as secure as possible. Access to your Personal Information is permitted among our employees only on a need-to-know basis, and any outside contractors with access to such information must first sign a confidentiality agreement with us.
CHANGES IN OUR POLICY
Givex reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. Whenever we make any alteration to this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes here. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.
WHO TO CONTACT
Please write to us at privacy-officer@givex.com or Attention: Privacy Officer, Givex, 1400-134 Peter St., Toronto, Ontario, M5V 2H2 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, or to do any of the following:
to see Personal Information you have already sent us so that you can correct or update it;
to ask that we delete your Personal Information from our records;
to correct or update Personal Information that your child under the age 18 has sent us;
to ask that we delete from our records Personal Information that your child under age 13 has sent us;
to ask that we not send you mailings or otherwise contact you;
to report any violations of the Privacy Policy.
Again, Givex is committed to protecting your privacy in connection with this web site. Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy.
We use cookies to analyze our web traffic and to help speed up your use of our site, for example by using any information you previously provided to auto-fill online forms. We do not share any information about your use of our site with any third parties. You consent to our cookies if you continue to use our website.
agree
